Mss.B.Sm95
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to [Frederick] Smith [Smyth], April 3, 1777; 6-3/4x7-1/2; Pigot, Robert
    New York, L.in 3rd.P. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) The request that John Dennis be released on parole has been granted.
  - Letter to [Frederick] Smyth, New York, April 10, 1778; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Howe, Richard Howe, Earl, 1726-1799
    Sandy Hook, A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Friendly letter. Concerning Wilmot.
  - Letter to Earl of Carlisle, Sir Henry Clinton, William Eden and George Johnstone, Sept. 17, 1778; 12-3/4x8; Smyth, Frederick, 1732-1815
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Wishes to know if he should leave for England. On same sheet is copy of reply; Sept. 21, 1778.
  - Letter to Frederick Smyth, Sept. 21, 1778; 12x7-1/2; Clinton, Henry, Sir, 1738?-1795
    New York, L.S.: Carlisle, H.Clinton, Wm.Eden and Geo. Johnstone. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) ----copy on same sheet as letter from Smyth to Clinton, et al; Sept. 17, 1778. Recommends he stay in America.
  - Letter to Frederick Smith [Smyth], Jan. 23, 1779; 12-1/2x7-3/4; Grey, Thomas de, jr.
    Whitehall, L.S. 2p. Duplicate. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) ----Copy in Smyth's hand. Cannot grant him more money. On same sheet is memorandum of monies received from H. Clinton; Oct.25,1779.
  - Memorandum of monies received by Frederick Smyth, Oct. 25, 1779; 12-1/2x7-3/4; Clinton, H[enry, Sir, 1738?-1795
    D.in Smyth's hand. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) On same sheet with letter from de Grey to Smyth; Jan. 23, 1779.
  - Letter to Frederick Smith [Smyth], March 9, 1780; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Simpson, John
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Informs him that he is to serve on a commission with Clinton. On same sheet is draft of letter from [Smyth] to Simpson; March 24, 1780.
  - Letter to [John Simpson], March 24, 1780; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Smyth, Frederick, 1732-1815
    New York, L.S. 1p. Draft. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Will be glad to serve with Clinton. On same sheet as letter from Simpson to Smyth; March 24, 1780.
  - Letter of attorney to Frederick Smyth, Dec. 6, 1781; 13x8-1/4; Simpson, John
    D.S. Witnessed: R. Sandby and A.Holm. Notarized: Claud[iu]s Holm. 2p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.)
  - Certification of John Simpson's letter of attorney to Frederick Smyth, Dec. 18, 1781; 13x8-1/2; Sandby, Robert
    London, D.S. witnessed: Wm.Plomer, Mayor, 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.)
  - Letter to William Seton, New York, March 15, 1783; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Rutherfurd, Walter
    Edgerston, A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Business. Refers to Smyth.
  - Letter to Fred[er]ick Smyth, May 21, 1783; 9-1/2x7; Livingston, William, 1723-1790
    Burlington, A.L.S. 2P. (see Frederick Smyth Papers.) There is no need for a passport to cross Jersey.
  - Letter to Frederick Smyth, May 23, 1783; 12x8-1/2; Kinsey (?)
    L. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Concerning the need of a passport of cross Jersey.
  - Letter to Fre[derick] Smyth, June 2, 1783; 9x7-1/2; Dickinson, John, 1732-1808
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Grants him permission to visit Pennsylvania.
  - Letter to Frederick Smyth, Philadelphia, Sept. 25, 1783; 9-1/4x7-1/4; Affleck, Edward
    New York, A.L.S. 3p.and add. ( see Frederick Smyth Papers.) Concerning the refugees going to Nov a Scotia. Refers to George Meade. News of friends.
  - Letter to W[illia]m Manning, Norfolk, May 19, 1784; 9x7-1/2; St. Vincent, John Jervis, Viscount, 1735-1823
    A.L.S. 2p.and add.,end. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Thinks Frederick Smyth will be taken care of.
  - Letter to [Frederick] Smyth, Dec. 29, 1784; 9x7-1/4; Penn, John, 1729-1795
    L.S.: John Penn, Edw[ard] Shippen and Th Thomas Parke. 3p.and end.: No.3. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Business matters concerning the estate.
  - Will, Aug. 15, 1785; 12-3/4x8; Smyth, Frederick, 1732-1815
    D.S. Witnessed: Geo[rge] Clymer, Henry Hill and Henry Clymer. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.)
  - Letter to Fred[eric]k Smyth, Jan. 5, 1786; 9x7-1/2; Morris, Robert, 1734-1806
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Business letter.
  - Statement pertaining to the will of Joseph Turner, April 4, 1789; 11-1/2x9; Ingersoll, Jared, 1749-1822 (Box Oversize)
    A.D.S. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Concerning Frederick Smyth's ability to transfer certain lands.
    General note
    See Oversize
  - Letter to Frederick Smyth, Philadelphia, July 17, 1789; 9x7-1/4; Penn, John, 1729-1795
    L.S. 2p.and add. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Hopes his business goes well.
  - Certificate of membership issued to Frederick Smyth, April 27, 1791; 9-1/2x11-1/2; Society of the Sons of St. George (Box Oversize)
    D.S.: Rob[er]t Morris, president, Dan[ie]l Rundle, treasurer; by order, A. Humphreys, secy. 1p. Seal. Parchment. (see Frederick Smyth papers.)
  - Letter to Frederick Smyth, Feb. 23, 1810; 5x7-3/4; Cadwalader, Thomas, 1779-1841
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Business.
  - Permission to stay in Philadelphia for one month to Fred[eric]k Smyth, March 18, 1813; 13-1/4x8; Pennsylvania. Marshall
    Philadelphia, Printed D. filled in in ms.S. 1p. Signed Frinith(?), Jo[h]n. (see Frederick Smyth papers.)
  - Letter to Frederick Smith [Smyth], Oct. 14, 1813; 10-1/4x8; Hopkinson, Joseph, 1770-1842
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Thanks him for donation to the Pennsylvania academy of the fine arts.
  - Note to ----, Nov. 25, 1816; 5x5; Chew, Benjamin, 1758-1844
    A.N.S. 1p. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Gives birth date for Mrs. Frederick Smyth as 1736.
  - Letter to Frederick Smyth, undated; 9x7-1/2; Clymer, George, 1739-1813
    Saturday noon. A.L.S. 2p.and add. (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Business.
  - Letter to [Frederick Smyth], undated; 12-1/2x8; Dudley, Charles
    Monday evening. L.S. 1p. Copy? (see Frederick Smyth papers.) Concerning the appointment of a man as a judge.